https://www.theroyalstore.com/privacy-policy-i-3.html

Royal Lace®Doilies
Doilies, Baking Cups & Shelf LinersCraft Doilies & Placemats Royal LaceBaking Cups Royal LaceShelf Liners
Royal Brites®Display Board
Royal Brites Display BoardPoster Board Royal BritesFoam BoardProject Board Science FairPoster Board Accessories
Recommended
Poster Board Fluorescent Neon Assorted Colors, 14"x22", 5/PK
As low as $3.89
Add to cart
Foam Board Sandstone/Greystone, 2 Cool Colors, 20"x30", 5/Case
Geographics®Certificates
Award Certificates & FramesGeographics CertificatesGeographics Foil SealsGeographics Document CoversDiploma Frames
Recommended
Blue Spiral Certificate Kit, 8.5"x11", 25/PK
As low as $11.99
Add to cart
Burgundy Classic Linen Document Covers, Gold Foil, 9.75"x12.5", 6/PK
As low as $10.99
Add to cart
Navy Blue Linen Window Document Covers, Gold Foil, 9.75"x12.5", 5/PK
As low as $10.99
Add to cart
Geographics®Stationery
Stationery by HolidayChristmas StationeryValentines Stationery4th of July StationeryThanksgiving StationeryHalloween StationeryStationery by ThemeWedding StationeryGraduation StationeryBirthday & Party StationerySchool StationeryFloral, Nature, Religious StationeryPrintable StationeryBusiness StationeryDesign PaperFine PaperBlank CardsPrintable CardsPrintable InvitationsEnvelopesMailing Labels & Seals
Recommended
Pinecones Christmas Letterhead, Red Foil, 8.5"x11", 40/PK
As low as $10.99
Add to cart
Brights Envelopes Assorted, No.10, (4.12"x9.5"), 25/PK
As low as $4.99
Add to cart
Apple, School Design Paper, 8.5"x11", 100/PK
As low as $7.99
Add to cart
The SchoolCorner
School CornerAward Certificates & SealsCertificate CoversCertificate FramesSchool Design PaperPoster BoardProject BoardFoam BoardPoster Accesssories
Recommended
Poster Board Fluorescent Neon Assorted 2 Cool Colors, 22"x28", 32/Case
As low as
$26.99
Add to cart
Alphabet, School Award Certificates, 8.5"x11", 100/PK
As low as $7.99
Add to cart
Black and White Words Award Certificates, 65 lb, 8.5"x11", 25/PK
As low as $8.99
Add to cart
Office &Technology
Office & School SuppliesFile & Storage CabinetsFile Folders, Portable & Storage Box FilesForms, Recordkeeping & Reference MaterialsGeneral Office AccessoriesIdentification BadgesIndex DividersLabels & StickersPaper & Printable MediaPresentation/Display & Scheduling BoardsRoom AccessoriesSafety & SecurityShipping & MailroomShredders & AccessoriesStamps & Stamp SuppliesStaplers & PunchesTags & TicketsTape, Adhesives & FastenersToolsWriting & Correction SuppliesArts & CraftsEnvelopes, Mailers & Shipping SuppliesSchool Classroom MaterialsTechnologyAudio Visual Equipment & AccessoriesBackup Systems & DisksBatteries & Electrical SuppliesCalculatorsComputer CleanersComputer Hardware & AccessoriesComputer Keyboards & MiceData Storage Media & SuppliesElectronicsImaging Supplies & PartsLaminator & Laminator SuppliesMobile Devices and AccessoriesMouse Pads & Wrist RestsNetworking, Cables & AccessoriesPaper & Printable MediaPrinter AccessoriesPrinters & Copier/Fax/Multifunction MachinesShredders & AccessoriesTelephones & Telephone AccessoriesToolsTranscription & Transcription AccessoriesWarranties
Recommended
Dry Erase Sentence Strips, 12 x 3, Assorted, 20 per Pack
$5.86
Add to cart
Astrobrights Colored Paper, 24lb, 11 x 17, Re-Entry Red, 500 Sheets/Ream
$37.49
Add to cart
Maintenance& Breakroom
Maintenance & BreakroomCOVID-19 Facial Masks & Cleaning SuppliesAir Cleaners, Fans, Heaters & HumidifiersAppliancesBags & LinersBatteries & Electrical SuppliesBeveragesBreakroom SuppliesCarts & StandsCleaning ProductsCleaning ToolsCups, Plates & UtensilsDollies & Hand TrucksFirst Aid & Health SuppliesFoodHardware, Tools & AccessoriesIndustrial SuppliesPersonal Hygiene ProductsRestroom Cleaners & AccessoriesSafety & SecurityTowels & TissuesWaste Receptacles & Accessories
Recommended
Face Masks Disposable 3-Layers, 10/PK
As low as
$11.00
Add to cart
Protective Face Shields, 5/PK
As low as
$14.90
Privacy Policy
www.theroyalstore.com, a 5A Plus, llc company respects the privacy of your personal and financial information. Our online shopping environment is private and secure.
This privacy policy is intended to help you understand how our system works and what safeguards are in place to protect your privacy.
COLLECTION AND USE OF CUSTOMERS' INFORMATION: By using this site, you agree to TheRoyalStore.com' collection and use of your information according to the terms described on this privacy page, and elsewhere in this Web site. We will post any changes to our privacy policy on this page, including what information is collected, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
When you make a purchase at TheRoyalStore.com you will provide us with basic information like: name, e-mail address, shipping and billing address, ZIP code, phone,
company name, and credit card numbers. This allows us to process your transactions more efficiently and to offer you a better customer service experience. We also may collect additional information like your Internet service provider's address(ISP), the name of the Web page you came to us from, as well as your clicks and activity on our site. This tracking data helps us to understand how to make our web site user-friendlier and how offer more relevant products to our customers. TheRoyalStore.com may disclose account information when required by law, or when, in good faith, we need to protect the rights, property, or safety of TheRoyalStore.com, its customers, or others. Any other information collected  is strictly used for our marketing research purposes and although not mandatory, will be used exclusively by us to make your purchasing experience better.
Please note that the TheRoyalStore.com web site may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for these websites' privacy policies.
SALE OF INFORMATIONTheRoyalStore.com guarantees not to sell, trade, rent, or otherwise provide any of your personal information to any third party except as noted here to service shipments of ordered product.
We take all reasonable steps to protect our customers' personal information against loss, misuse and alteration. We use encryption technology whenever receiving and transferring our customers' personal information on our site. We have appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you. If you feel that this site is not following the policy, please contact us at support@theroyalstore.com or call us toll free at 1-800-436-4919.
COOKIESTheRoyalStore.com website requires the use of cookies for full access to the site. Cookies are small bits of information stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser and used to personalize your online experience. They sound friendly and helpful because they are. They flag information about your activity on our web site such as items that you add to your shopping cart. Both cookies and web beacons may be used in the tracking and monitoring of your readership levels and pass-along of an e-mail campaign. This information helps us improve our site's user friendliness features. We never use cookies to save passwords, credit card numbers, or other highly confidential information, but rather save your log in information for your convenience and provide content specific to your interests. The information gathered may be shared with advertisers or partners on an aggregate basis for broad demographic statistics, but none of it will personally identify you. If you choose to turn off cookies in your browser, you will be unable to use the Online Store features of our web site.
SECURE SOCKET LAYER: TheRoyalStore.com uses SSL technology, the industry's standard for secure e-commerce, to encrypt your name, address, and credit card number. SSL allows you to safely and securely enter sensitive information in your browser, and rest comfortably assured that your information will not be intercepted and decrypted while in transit.
FIREWALL: TheRoyalStore.com website is hosted behind an Internet firewall. Firewalls assist in the security of your data by limiting electronic access to the TheRoyalStore.com
server.
FAIR CREDIT BILLING ACTIf you pay with a credit card, the Fair Credit Billing Act states that your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. Of course, if you ever believe your credit card has been compromised, you should contact your credit card company immediately.
ONLINE STOREBecause a third-party shipper may handle our shipping, they will have access to your personal information, (name and address), but only to your personal information. Credit card information and record of your transaction are fully protected.
Continue
In order to proceed, you must login
Login
Forgot password?
New Customer Account
Open a Reseller Account
Open an EDU Account
2048 Bit SSL Certificate
